- 所以你跟瑞秋今晚有约？ - 是的
- So you and Rach tonight, huh?    - Yeah.
其实是我们第一次的正式约会
Yeah, it's actually our first official date.
所以今晚可能会有好事发生了 你会紧张吗？
Wow, so tonight may be the night. You nervous?
不会 这个部分我还蛮厉害的
Nah. No. This is the part I'm actually good at, ha, ha.
没有自我恐惧的感觉 到底是什么样呢？
What must it be like not to be crippled by fear and self-loathing?
还不错
It's okay.
你怎么能够这么有自信？
How can you be so confident?
因为我完全知道自己该怎么做
Well, I know exactly what I'm gonna do.
- 真的吗？你有惯用的招式吗？ - 不 其实每个女人都不同
- Really? Like, you have a routine?    - No. See, each woman is different.
你必须欣赏她们的独特点
You have to appreciate their uniqueness.
- 真的吗？ - 才怪 我有六个招式
- Really?     - No, I do six things.
首先 我深情的看着她 然后亲吻她
First, I look deep into her eyes, then I kiss her.
接着 我拿起我的手 轻轻地抚摸她的大腿
Next, I take my hand and I softly graze her thigh.
你的意思是像这样吗？
You mean like this?
不是 不是这样子 是像这样子
No, not like that. No, no. No, like this:
我知道你的意思了 感觉还蛮不错
I see what you mean. That's quite nice.
再来比一场手足球？
Ahem. More foosball?
- 还要啤酒   - 是
- And beer.      - Yeah.
（中央咖啡厅）
- 你好啊   - 你好
- Hey.     - Hey.
你好 亲爱的
Hey, sweetie.
哇
Wow.
嘿 不要再瞄我老婆的腿了
Hey, stop staring at my wife's legs.
不对…不要再瞄你妹妹的腿了
No, no. Stop staring at your sister's legs.
对不起 只是… 你怎么有办法晒这么漂亮？
I'm sorry, it's just... How'd you get so tan?
她去了一家用药剂把皮肤喷黑的店
She went to one of those spray-on tan places.
你用药剂喷黑皮肤吗？
You got a spray-on tan?
钱德去美容指甲
Chandler gets pedicures.
什么？你去美容指甲？有用脚趾分开器吗？
What? You do? Like, with the toe separators?
不行吗？不行吗？
Why? Why?
我不敢相信是喷上去的
I can't believe that's sprayed on.
看起来很漂亮 我想是不是应该也去试试看
I mean, it looks really good. I wonder if I should get one.
好啊 然后再去穿迷你裙 就可以上街炫耀了
Sure, then you should get a miniskirt so you can really show it off.
你是去上点指甲油 还是有做指甲彩绘？
So do you get colors or just French tips?
- 这是那边的名片   - 谢谢
- Here. Here's their card.     - Thanks.
嘿 我知道这个地方在哪
Hey, I know where this place is.
原本是一个色情录影带…
It used to be an X-rated video...
卖花的
Florist.
嘿
Hey.
- 你好    - 你好 菲比
- Hey, Pheebs.    - Hey, Phoebe.
你不会相信谁搬回了城里
Ugh, you won't believe who moved back to town.
- 我知道 阿曼达   - 额
- I know. Amanda.    - Ugh.
- 她也打电话给我了 她真是烂人   - 谁是阿曼达？
- She called me too. She's the worst.     - Who's Amanda?
她是在你之前住在你公寓里的人
She's this girl who lived in the building before you did.
然后她搬到了英国 学会了一个假英国腔
Then she moved to England and picked up this fake British accent.
在答录机里她这样留官
On the machine, this is her message:
"摩妮卡 亲爱的 我是阿曼达"
"Um, Monica, darling, it's Amanda calling."
你在假装英国腔吗？
Are you trying to do a British accent?
钱德去美容指甲
Chandler gets pedicures.
先让我知道一下 你还会跟多少人讲？
Just so I know, how many more of those can I expect?
你知道阿曼达打电话来时 跟我说了些什么吗？
Know what Amanda said when she called me?
"很抱歉 打你的手机才找到你"
"Oh, so sorry to catch you on your mobile."
如果你不想打手机找我 那就不要打我的手机
If you didn't wanna get me on my mobile, then don't call me on my mobile.
而且她每次都炫耀 她认识很多名人
And she always brags about all the famous people she's met.
对 我知道
Oh, I know.
"我跟比利乔睡过"
"Uh, I slept with Billy Joel."
够了 谁没跟他睡过？
All right, who hasn't?
我该怎么办 我真的不想见她
Oh, what are we gonna do? I don't wanna see her.
我们干脆来排挤她
Oh, let's just cut her out.
- 什么？ - 将她挤出我们生命中
- What?     - Cut her out of our lives.
不要接她的电话 冷落她到她懂了为止
Just ignore her calls and dodge her till she gets the point.
好吧 我想是可以试试看 但是这样好残忍
Well, I guess we could try that. But it seems so harsh.
- 你有试过这样做吗？ - 没有 倒有人对我这样做过
- Have you ever done that?     - No. Had it done to me, though.
感觉还蛮不错的
Feels good.
好了 盖勒先生 往这里走
All right, Mr. Geller, right this way.
你想要晒多黑？我们有一度 两度 三度黑
So how dark do you wanna be? We have one, two or three.
我喜欢你的肤色 你是几度？
Well, uh, I like how you look. What are you?
- 我是波多黎各人   - 二度好了
- Puerto Rican.     - Two. I think a two.
你要面向红灯
You'll face the red light.
当红灯亮起时 药将会喷出 所以你要闭起眼睛
When the light's on, the spraying's about to start, so close your eyes.
当药喷完时 数到五
When the spraying stops, count to five...
轻轻拍身体 避免有不均匀痕迹 然后转身换背后 懂了吗？
...pat yourself to avoid drip marks, then turn to get your back. Got it?
喷 数 拍 然后转身 喷 数 拍
Spray, count, pat and turn. Spray, count and pat.
- 你很快就学会了呢   - 因为我有博士学位 所以…
- Wow, you catch on quick.     - Well, I have a Ph.D., so...
一个密西西比 两个密西西比 三个…
One Mississippi, two Mississippi, three...
等等 我还没…我还没数完
Wait, wait! I'm not... I'm not finished counting.
你在我前面喷了两次
You sprayed my front twice.
- 你没有转身吗？ - 我还没数到"三个密西西比"
- You never turned?     - No. I barely got to "three Mississippi."
密西西比？我说数到五
Mississippi? I said count to five.
不用密西西比的方式吗？
Mississippi-lessly?
看起来会有多糟糕？
Well, how bad is it?
还不算太糟 但四小时之后会更黑
Not that bad yet. But it gets darker for the next four hours.
所以会有多黑？
So how dark will it get?
你喷了两次两度 所以…
Oh, you got sprayed with two twos and...
所以是四度吗？
I'm a four?
没错 但是背部是零度 所以你得平均一下
Yeah, but your back's a zero. You'll wanna even that out.
是这样吗？
Really?
- 你应该要回去里面   - 好吧
- You might wanna get back in there.      - Oh, okay.
等等 后面没有红灯啊
Wait a minute, there's no light on the back wall.
我怎么知道什么时候会开始喷？哈罗？
How do I know when it's gonna start? Hello?
我的眼睛
My eyes!
又发生了同样的事情了
The same thing happened again!
- 你又喷了两次两度？ - 我现在是八度了
- You got two more twos?     - I'm an eight.
谢谢你的晚餐
Thanks for dinner.
我以为是你付钱的
I thought you paid.
我猜以后不会再回去吃了
Heh. Guess we won't be going back there, ha, ha.
- 所以…   - 好的
- So...     - Yeah.
你想不想移过来躺到沙发上？
Hey, what do you say we, uh, move this onto the likes of the couch?
你的台词很烂 不过好啊
I say cheesy line, but okay.
- 你怎么了？ - 我不知道 对不起
- What's the matter?     - I don't know. I'm sorry.
- 我不知道为什么我会这么做   - 好吧
- I don't know why I did that.     - Okay.
好的 对不起
Okay. Sorry.
对不起 我还是不知道为什么 应该是太紧张吧
I'm sorry. Again, I don't know what happened. I must be nervous.
我不懂 钱德还蛮喜欢的
I don't get it. Chandler loved it.
好
Okay.
我保证不会再发生 真的 一定会很棒的
I promise. I won't do it again. I really do. This is gonna be great.
- 好   - 好
- Okay.      - Okay.
你喜欢这样吗？
Uh, was that good for you?
不 不要接 让答录机去回应吧
No, don't get it. Let the machine pick up.
好吧 说不定是瑞秋打来 问有没有人可以带小孩
Oh, yeah, it could be Rachel asking if someone could babysit again.
- 说不定是阿曼达   - 对 有道理
- It could be Amanda.     - Oh, you're right. Oh.
关于瑞秋 我只是开玩笑的 带小孩超级好玩的
I was just kidding about Rachel. Babysitting's a gas.
摩妮卡你好 是我阿曼达 又打来了
Hello, Monica. It's Amanda calling again.
我现在在附近 看看能不能去你家一趟
I'm in the neighborhood, hoping I could pop by your flat.
你是纽约人 你姓布发蒙提企
You're from Yonkers. Your last name is Buffamonteezi.
我想想 如果你收到了留言
Let's see. So should you get this directly...
直接打到我的手机吧
...ring me back on my mobile.
好了 你休想
Okay, don't hold thy breath.
喂？有人在电话上吗？
Hello? Is someone on the line?
是的 我找摩妮卡
Yes. I was looking for Monica.
等等 她在家
Hang on, she's right here.
- 有人打电话找你   - 我们不打算接起来 是阿曼达
- Someone's on the phone for you.     - We weren't picking up. It's Amanda.
我去美容指甲
I get pedicures.
阿曼达你好
Hi, Amanda.
其实现在不太方便
Uh, actually, now is not a good time.
- 明天晚上吃饭吗？ - 不
- Dinner tomorrow night?     -  No.
好的 菲比会跟我一起去
Okay, Phoebe and I will see you then.
为什么…为什么你没有拒绝？
Why? Why? Why didn't you just say no?
因为我已经拒绝她过来了 我不想拒绝两次
Well, I said no to her coming over now. I couldn't say no twice.
我控制不了自己不去讨好别人
I got this uncontrollable need to please people.
算了…你无法在酷刑中坚忍
Fine. Fine. You would not hold up well under torture.
- 你就可以吗？ - 我已经忍过了
- Oh, and you would?     - I did.
- 瑞秋 你确定要继续吗？ - 当然
- Rach, are you sure you wanna do this?     - Absolutely.
虽然有一点奇怪 但是有你 还有我
It's just a little weird. It's you, and it's me.
- 只要习惯一下就好    - 好的
- It'll just take some getting used to.     - Okay.
那我们用什么方法来解决？
Okay, well, uh, how can we make it easier?
好 不如从头开始吧
Okay. Let's work from the top down.
- 把我的胸罩解开 乔伊   - 好… 我知道了
- Just work the bra, Joe.     - Okay, got it, yeah. Absolutely.
- 好的   - 好
- Okay, ha, ha.      - Okay.
- 这个东西是锁起来了吗？ - 别闹了
- Is this thing welded shut? Ha, ha.     - Okay.
好吧 转过来
All right, turn around.
- 我要看看这是什么   - 哦
- I gotta get a look at this thing.     - Oh.
- 哦   - 抱歉
- Ow!     - Sorry.
这还真是浪漫呢
Well, this is romantic.
对不起 这种事情从来没发生在我身上过
I'm sorry. This has never happened to me before.
我是解胸罩的专家 我一只手就能解开了
I'm an expert at taking off bras. I could do it with one hand.
我甚至闭着眼睛都能解开 有一次我只是看了一眼…
I could do it with my eyes closed. Once I just looked at one...
然后就解开了
...and it popped open.
- 都怪你的胸罩   - 这是普通的胸罩夹呢
- I blame your bra.     - It's a standard-issue bra clasp.
那就是你的错了 对 你的巴掌让我冷成
Then I blame you. Yeah. That's right. You threw me off with all your slapping.
好…我真的很抱歉 乔伊
Okay, look, I'm really sorry about that, Joey.
但是你不觉得在某种程度 你不想要脱掉我的胸罩吗？
But do you think maybe, on some level, you don't want to take off my bra?
不可能 我没有其他程度了
No, I don't have another level.
等等 你有点不同
Hold on. There's something different.
我去了你老婆介绍的晒黑地方
I went to that tanning place your wife suggested.
那个地方是在太阳上面吗？
Was that place the sun?
而且还有更糟的
Oh, and it gets worse.
我的天啊 你可以自己一个人 合唱一首《乌木与象牙》
Oh, my God, you can do a duet of "Ebony and lvory" all by yourself.
你怎么会搞砸呢？明明很简单
How could you mess this up? It's so easy.
你进去小房间里 数到五然后转身
You go in the booth, count to five and turn around.
- 你怎么数的？ - 一 二 三…
- How do you count to five?     - One, two, three...
可恶
Damn it!
- 我知道   - 哈哈哈
- I know!     - Ha-ha-ha.
这位夏威夷小姐发生了什么事？
Oh, what is up with Miss Hawaiian Tropic?
你跟乔伊的约会如何？
How was your date with Joey?
本来还不错 直到我们回到了公寓里
Well, it was good, until we got back to our apartment.
然后我们开始有点激情 接着他开始把手放在我腿上
And then we were fooling around and he started to put his hand up my leg...
然后我一直把他手打掉
...and I kept slapping it away.
你居然会不喜欢被那样摸？
You didn't like that?
也不只是我的问题 好吗？他也怪怪的
Well, it wasn't just me, all right? He freaked out too.
他连我的胸罩都解不开
He couldn't even undo my bra.
真的吗？有一次他只看了 我的胸罩一眼 然后就爆开了
Wow, really? One time he just looked at my bra and it popped open.
我不知道我们的问题在哪
I do not know what's wrong with us.
我们接吻过 感觉很好
We've kissed before and that's been great.
但这一次有多一点进展了
But this time it was leading somewhere...
而且我很清楚是乔伊在碰我
...and I was very aware of the fact that it was Joey touching me.
你们是老朋友了
You guys have been friends forever.
记得你第一次跟罗斯接吻也很怪
The first time you kissed Ross was weird.
- 嗯   - 你笑得停不下来
- Mm-hm.     - You couldn't stop laughing.
- 但是后来还是解决了  - 嗯
- You got through that.     - Mm-hm.
对 你说的对 真的 我们可以解决的
Okay. That's true. That's true, we can do this.
没错 我们可以解决的 我们只需要突破
You're right. We can do this. We'll just power through.
钱德 我可以跟你聊一下吗？
Hey, uh, Chandler, can I talk to you for a second?
不必 问题解决了 我们要突破
No need, problem solved. We are powering through.
钱德 别闹了 它不会自己爆开
Chandler, stop. It's not going to pop open.
很难说
You don't know.
- 菲比 你好   - 你好
- Hi, Phoebe.     - Hey.
- 阿曼达来了没？ - 还没
- Is Amanda here yet?     - No.
抱歉我把排挤她的计划搞砸了 但是我有新的计划
I'm sorry for screwing up that "cutting her out" plan, but I have a new plan.
钱德几分钟后会打电话过来 说有紧急的事情
Chandler will call in a few minutes with an emergency.
什么样的紧急事情 可以让我们逃离这里？
Oh, okay, what kind of emergency gets us both out of here?
如果说麦克跟钱德发生车祸呢？
What do you think of Mike and Chandler being in a car accident?
- 真的吗？我爱死了这计划    - 好的
- Are you kidding? I love it.     - Okay.
- 你好   - 你好
- Hi. Ha, ha.    - Hi.
你好啊
Hello.
- 看到你感觉真棒   - 哈哈
- It's so nice to see you.    - Ha, ha.
你们两个 看看我 看看我样子多年轻
Both of you, look at me. Look how young I look.
老天 我们有好多事要聊
Oh, gosh, we have so much to catch up on.
但是先摸摸看我的腹肌 我根本没运动呢
But first things first. Touch my abs. I don't exercise at all.
天啊 摩妮卡 你结婚了
Oh, gosh. So, Monica, you're married.
- 对啊 他的名字是钱德 他是…   - 闻闻我的脖子
- Yeah, his name is Chandler and he's...     - Oh, smell my neck.
这不是香水呢 是体味 是我身体天然的香味
It's not perfume. It's me. It's my natural scent.
- 还有霉味呢  - 哦
- Musty.     - Oh.
天啊 真是太好了 老天 就像以前一样
Gosh, this is brilliant. Gosh, it's just like old times.
我真高兴你们两个人又是朋友了
I'm so happy you two are friends again.
- 我们哪时不是朋友了？ - 当时是1992年
- When were we not friends?    - Well, it was 1992.
而我记得很清楚 因为那年我跟伊佛克尼莫上床
And I remember, because that was the year I had sex with Evel Knievel. Ha, ha.
在1992年我们还是朋友
Uh, we were friends in 1992.
不 我记的很清楚 你正在躲她的电话
No, I distinctly remember you were dodging her calls...
而且试着不见她
...and trying to avoid seeing her.
- 你当时正在排挤我吗？ - 有一点点啦
- You were going to cut me out?     - Well, kind of.
- 我的老天啊   - 糟了
- Oh, my God.     - Oh, bugger.
我是不是不应该讲出来？ 我觉得自己很驴
Should I not have said that? Unh! I feel like a perfect arse.
在美国你只是个猪头
Well, in America, you're just an ass.
喂？
Hello?
钱德？发生什么事？
Chandler, what's wrong?
我的天啊 你还好吗？好 我马上到
Oh, my God, are you all right? Yeah, I'll be right there.
抱歉 但是钱德发生车祸了
Oh, I'm so sorry, but Chandler was in a car accident.
- 我的老天啊   - 是啊
- Oh, my God.     - Yeah.
- 麦克跟他在一起吗？ - 没有
- Was Mike with him?     - Nope.
- 嘿    - 嘿
- Hey.     - Hi.
- 有准备香槟吗？ - 有 准备好要来突破了
- Got the champagne?     - Yes. Ready to power through.
太好了 放进冰块里 电话线也被拉掉了
Excellent. Put it on ice, the phone is off the hook...
而关于突破的事…
...and, in the interest of powering through...
好的 性感…
Okay, sexy, sexy.
非常性感
Very sexy, sexy.
- 好的 开始吧   - 你把我吓到了
- All right, let's do it.   - Okay, you're scaring me a little bit.
- 回神来 小兵 我们得进行了   - 好的
- Oh, get over it, soldier, we gotta do this.    - Okay.
- 好 你喜欢吗？ - 太棒了
- Okay. Ha, ha, you like that, huh?     - Oh, yeah.
你喜欢吗 再来点更刺激的吧
You like that? Let's kick this into high gear, huh?
噢 噢
Oh. Oh.
太好了 宝贝 让你看看该怎么做
Yeah, baby. I'll show you how we do it.
不要…
No, no, no.
你跪在我的小宝贝上面了
You kneed me in my misters.
什么？我的天啊 我很抱歉
What? Oh, my God. I'm so sorry.
乔伊？你还好吧？
Joey? Are you okay?
小兵倒下来了
Soldier down.
我们再也不跟菲比做朋友了
We are not friends with Phoebe anymore.
如果她问起 就说我抗拒过了一下 不过好吧
If she asks, I protested a little, but okay.
钱德 感谢老天 你还活着 摩妮卡 我可以跟你聊聊吗？
Oh, Chandler, thank God you're alive. Monica, can I talk to you outside?
- 我没什么话好跟你说   - 我的公寓是这里的两倍大
- I have nothing to say to you.     - Wow. My flat is twice this size.
拜托你 摩妮卡 到走廊来
Please, Monica, in the hall?
那场车祸一定很惨烈
Ooh, that accident must have been terrible.
你看起来很苍白
You look positively ghastly.
你还真是个好人呢
Well, aren't you a treat.
我不敢相信你居然排挤我 为什么？菲比 为什么？
I can't believe you tried to cut me out. Why, Phoebe? Why?
这是在我们当过室友之后
It was right after we were living together...
而你快把我搞疯了 好吗？
...and you were driving me crazy, okay?
你控制欲太强 又爱强迫人 讲话又大声
You were really controlling and compulsive and shrill.
我现在还是这样啊
Well, I'm still all those things.
你也很慷慨 和蔼和好斗
You're also so generous and kind and scrappy.
我的确很好斗
I am scrappy.
没错 不管我怎么做 我的人生就是不能没有你
Exactly. No matter what I tried to do, I couldn't keep you out of my life.
所有我排挤的人当中
Of all the people I've cut out...
你是唯一一个还张牙舞爪回来的人
...you were the only one who ever clawed her way back in.
那是因为我很好斗
That's because I'm scrappy.
是的 而且我很高兴你这样子 一路战斗着回来
Yeah, you are, and I'm so glad that you fought your way back in...
因为我不知道没有你 我该怎么办
...because I don't know what I would do without you.
我也不知道没有你 我该怎么办
I don't know what I would do without you.
哦
Oh.
我想我们该进去了 我是说 你给了我另一个机会
Well, I guess we should go back in. I mean, you gave me another chance.
- 我们应该也这样对待阿曼达   - 我想你说的对
- We should do the same for Amanda.     - Yeah, I guess you're right.
你能相信吗？我从来没有职业舞蹈训练
Can you believe it? I've never had any professional dance training.
让我解释使用方法 你进去小房间里 然后…
Let me explain how this works. Go in the booth and...
你不用说了 葛兰达
I'm gonna stop you right there, Glenda. Okay? Ha, ha.
我看起来像是第一次来吗？
Does it look like this is my first time, huh?
我要四个两度 全部喷在我的背上
Now, I want four two's, and I want them all on my back.
好的
Okay.
等一下 两边都有喷嘴 哪边才是对的…？
Wait. There's two sets of nozzles. Which one is it? Which one is it?
可恶 他妈的
Oh, son of a bitch!
我们的问题出在哪里？
What is the matter with us?
至少我知道自己怎么了
Well, I know what's the matter with me.
我的意思是说我们两个 真的应该这么…
No, I mean with us, you know? I mean, is it supposed to be this...
困难吗？
...difficult?
我不知道
I don't know.
那个假英国女人是个贱货 但她还真会跳舞
That fake British woman's a real bitch, but she sure can dance.
- 你们好   - 你好啊
- Hey.    - Hi.
听着 我想问你一个问题 你一开始跟摩妮卡交往时
Hey, listen, can I ask you a question? When you and Monica first hooked up...
超过了好友的界线之后 会不会很奇怪？
...was it weird going from friends to more than that?
有一点点 要偷偷摸摸的 还得躲你们
Kind of. Sneaking around, having to hide from you guys...
不是…我是说…
No, no, no. No, I mean...
在性的方面
...sexually.
对啊 某一部分你会觉得有点…
Yeah, uh, was there a part of you that felt like it was...
不太对劲吗？
...really wrong?
其实不会 其实感觉是对的
Actually, no. No, it felt right, you know?
感觉像是
If felt like, uh:
"我们居然没有早点这么做"
"I can't believe we haven't been doing this the whole time."
我可以从你们脸上的表情看出 这是你们想要的好消息
I can tell from your expressions that's the good news you were hoping for.
好吧 我继续来散播这些喜悦
Well, I'm gonna go continue to spread the joy.
虽然他们的状况是这样 不代表我们也应该这样
Just because it happened that way for them doesn't mean it has to for us.
当然了
Yeah. Yeah, absolutely.
就算遇到了困难 也不代表得放弃
I mean, just because something's difficult doesn't mean that you quit.
- 就是说啊   - 没错
- Right, totally.     - Yeah. And so...
所以我们只要继续尝试 直到真的成功了
...we'll just keep trying and trying until we do it.
如果不行的话 我们就变成 没有性生活的情侣好了
If not, we'll just be a couple that never has sex.
这也是个方案
That's a plan.
- 我不知道结果会这样   - 我也是
- I did not see this coming.     - I know.
我不知道 我不懂 我很确定这就是我要的
I don't know, I don't get it. I mean, I was so sure this is what I wanted.
嗯
Mm-hm.
我也是
Me too.
那为什么摩妮卡跟钱德就可以呢？
Well, how come Monica and Chandler could do it?
也许他们的友情没有我们来得深
I guess they weren't as good friends as we are.
喔
Aw.
- 我想你说对了 - 嗯
- I bet you're right.     - Hmm.
所以…
So...
怎样？
Yeah.
我爱你
I love you.
我也爱你
Love you too.
- 好了 我要去睡了   - 我也是
- All right, I'm going to bed.     - Yeah, me too.
好 我暂时哪里也不去
Yeah. I'm not going anywhere for a while.
- 老兄 我是钱德 让我进去   - 走开
- It's Chandler. Let me in.     - Go away.
我谁也不想见
I don't wanna see anybody.
我知道 我也去了那间店 同样的事情也发生在我身上
I went to the tanning place and the same thing happened to me.
让我进去
Let me in.
真的吗？
Really?
你也用密西西比的方式算数吗？
Did you count Mississippi-ly?
你根本没变黑
You're not tan.
没有 我只是来拍个照 再见
No. I just had to get a picture of this. I'll see you later.